Thank you for watching!
Good evening everyone. The morning chime has rung. It's us, the Shiri Seiri Naka Role.
Yes, before we start the program, I would like to choose today's MC.
Yes, we have a choice between 1 and 2.
Please vote for your favorite between 1 and 2.
Yes, sir. The person who has the program card with that number on it is the MC.
Yes, sir.
There are only two.
It's two people.
We chose this one.
Good evening.
Yuna took the liberty of following me today.
It was put on without permission.
It's cute.
Voting is underway.
Mr. Ki said my hair is cute.
Thank you. I had it done 10 minutes before I left home today.
Start!
Voting has started!
It hadn't started at all. I'm going to keep talking.
I was talking.
Voting has started, hasn't it?
Yu is often the MC in the showroom,
You know, at the showroom.
When I'm allowed to do it,
Oh, no, it's not that.
I still make mistakes.
There were many of them.
When it comes to voting, it's always "YU". When it comes to voting, it's definitely going to be YU.
That's right.
I guess they thought that Yuto should be the MC in the showroom, didn't they? Everyone thought so.
I was thinking of doing it again.
That's right.
I understand.
I'm thinking, "Should I do it now?
Not yet.
Yes, I do.
Four. Four.
One. One.
Aaaaah!
Is it my turn?
Yes, sir.
Yes, I see.
Ho!
Okay, let me show you something.
Ready?
Yes, sir.
Yes!
Okay, I'm number 2.Yes, I'm number two.
I will be the MC.
My name is Nanoko Kazami, attendance number 15.
I look forward to working with you.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Yes, and?
Yes, I'm number 14, Kokoyama.
Pleased to meet you.
Yes, sir.
Let's start with the showroom of Shrimps.
Today is all fine and dandy. Thank you very much for watching the 62nd Hilarious and Humorous Showroom of the Shrimps.
The showroom is the sister showroom of our sister showroom, Uka's showroom.
So, it's time to spread the word! In order to get as many people as possible to watch this show, we're going to make an announcement on the official Ebichu website right now.
I'm going to make that announcement on the official Ebichu x page, so please spread the word!
Manager, please spread the word!
Oh, great!
Thank you very much.
This might be my first time.
I'm not an MC by vote.
Yes, it is.
That's great. Finally.
I wonder why they were so obvious. The numbers.
I guess so.
I'm a little confused.
Today. Let's have him take it easy.
Okay. I'm looking forward to it.
So, I would like to go to the project.
Today's project is like this.
The title is,
A funny and huffy survey talk. Hilarious and huuuuuuge survey talk.
Yay.
Yes. Take the survey before you post,
decide what to talk about.
That's what Survey Talk is all about.
So, this time.
This is what it looks like.
We wrote a lot of columns.
There are a lot of columns that we wrote.
We have written a lot of columns.
Please vote for what you like.
I hope you will vote for what you like,
I hope you will vote for what you like.
I hope you will all vote for what you like.
Here we go. Let's get started.
Oh, I did it.
That's great. It's interesting that it's easy to tell which way the letters are written, isn't it?
Yes, it is. It's really easy to tell.
But, tomorrow is the Orquera Disco, right?
That's right, it's tomorrow. Finally, everyone.
I know, right?
Oh no, really.
I wonder what song they're going to play.
It's true. I wonder what song they're going to play.
I wonder.
Well, you know.
I wonder what song they're going to play.
Please enjoy it.
Amazing.
Amazing. The last sound, the masked master...what's up with that? That's amazing. The last sound, or the masked master, or whatever.
I'm curious about the masked master text, though.
Really? Really? I think Yuna-san knows the story.
Ah.
Oh, it's over.
Oh, you're done.
It's over. Yes, I'm done. Let's see.
Number 6 is in first place.
Number 6. Tortoisebug.
I'm curious about that. About the turtle bug.
This is something I wrote,
This is a story about an interesting event that happened quite a while ago.
There was a concert on the 25th of August,
That night, there was an event.
I was allowed to participate in a music video live performance,
I was relaxing at home that night,
Suddenly, there is a line group called Techo Taru with 10 members,
All 10 members joined.
Suddenly, Kaho sent me a picture of Kamemushi,
She sent it to me.
She said, "I have a turtle bug at home, what should I do?
She said, "I have a turtle bug at home, but what should I do?
And then, everyone sent him a message saying, "Try this, try this, try this,
In the end, Riko's paper cup or something was used to cover it up for the time being,
Then, I took it out from under her with something like an underlay,
I sent it to Riko, and she said she wanted to try it,
So, they decided to give it a try,
He said he tried that, but it was quite a struggle,
He said he had been struggling with it for one or two hours.
And he was right in the middle of the room. And he was right in the middle of the room.
I can't go anywhere.
I can't go anywhere, really.
So they were wondering what to do.
That was very interesting to me.
And you know, when Kaho-chan was wondering how to get him to let her go,
I think this is probably a kokane bug,
I think it's probably a kokane bug.
She sent it to me, and it was very interesting.
But I'm glad to hear that you were able to get it out safely.
That's good.
But how do you let the stinkbugs go when they come out?
I asked my mothers,
I asked my moms.
What about Yuru?
Yuru pinched him with the vacuum cleaner.
Wait! Poor thing.
That was it. That's his house, right?
His room was almost like a storage room at his house.
I was cleaning it out,
I was cleaning it up, and it was turned upside down and probably no longer alive,
I thought it might be a good idea to let it go.
That's true.
It would have been a little bit awkward to leave it outside.
But I also met my grandfather.
Grandfather?
I also met a cockroach.
Oh, yeah!
Not in Yuu's room. It's not Yuu's room.
They showed a video of Yuuno's father fighting with cockroaches.
It was amazing.
He was spraying and stuff.
They were taking a video of Yuuno laughing.
It was interesting.
There are lots of insects in summer, but it's already getting cold.
I got crab bites yesterday.
Yesterday, my knee was swollen like crazy,
It probably wasn't a mosquito.
So I thought it might have been a different kind of insect, disguised as a mosquito.
Yuuno's knee,
If there was someone who knew more about it, that would be scary,
It's bony, or rather, it's crunched, right?
But thanks to the crab bite, it's nicely protected.
The knee is the point of the wound.
If you think your left knee is rounded tomorrow, that's what I'm talking about,
That's what I mean. It's a crab bite.
You should think of it that way, too.
That's what I meant.
Let's move on to the next topic.
Okay, the survey.
Also, I heard that the same content is okay.
So let's go to Kamebashi one more time.
Even if we go to Kamebashi one more time.
I don't know what to do.
Katte, that's it.
It's too hot, this year, too.
Yeah.
That's why I'm coming out now. That's why it's coming out now.
It's like, summer was too hot, so it's coming out now.
I don't like it.
When it gets too cold, you get bugs again, don't you?
At lunchtime, for example.
Even today's lunchtime is very different from today's, isn't it?
That's right.
Seriously, it's so cold in the morning and at night that I was surprised at how cold it was without a thick futon.
Even in summer, you need a thick comforter.
That's it. That's it.
But I don't have the air conditioner on right now.
It's nice and cold even without air conditioning.
That's true.
It's just right.
Just right.
Let me take a good look at your knee.
I don't want to.
There were tortoiseshells at FAMIA, weren't there?
Yes, there were.
When it gets dark, they gather at the light.
Then it's over.
That's that,
I wonder what happened.
I wonder what's next.
Oh!
Okera Disco.
Tomorrow is Okela Disco 2023!
I have to tell you about this, don't I?I have to talk about this, don't I?
It's tomorrow, everyone.
Will you all come?
Yes, they will.
They'll come. You know what?
If you watch our showroom, too.
Of course.
Of course, of course. Please have fun.
What do you think of the orchestra disco?
We had rehearsals with the orchestra,
It was the first time for me to try something like this,
I think I won't know what to expect until we actually do it.
Magnificent.
Yes! Really!
Today, until now.
And live, not at all.
We did a tossy rehearsal at rehearsal, remember?
I didn't have a huge muscle ache in my knee after the tossy rehearsal.
That's for sure!
I don't know,
I don't usually get sore muscles when I dance like that,
I don't usually get sore muscles from dancing like that, but for some reason, my muscles were sore above the knees.
And different movements, too. I might have done some of them.
I'm doing moves I don't usually do.
Yes, that's right. That's for sure.
That may be true.
I think I'm going to do that kind of thing.
I'm going to go on my knees.Go above the knee.
I'm going to go on my knees.
If you are going to dance together with me, please be careful not to go above your knees,
If you are going to dance along with the choreography, please be careful to stay above your knees.
There was really some light effects, wasn't there?
Yes!
As Maima-san said on the radio,
There were lasers and bees and so on.
We haven't seen how the light was like yet, so we'll see tomorrow at the rehearsal,
We'll see at tomorrow's rehearsal.
We will find out at the rehearsal.
I'm looking forward to it!
I'm nervous about performing indoors without a fenlight.
I'm okay with towels and stuff,
Please use towels or hands or something.
Way, way, way.
Everyone is free to dance.
It's amazing, isn't it?
I remember how great it was at the reboot.
Yes, it was.
This time it was a little different from the director of the reboot.
It's the usual Kineo-san,
He's a bumblebee.
I wonder how it will turn out. We'll see what happens.
It's Mr. Kineo's laser bachi-bachi.
It's a bumblebee for the first time.
I don't know what's going to happen. I don't know.
Maybe some of you might wonder how it will be,
I'm sure it will be a fun concert.
There are some songs that I wish the orchestra played.There are songs that I wish had been performed by an orchestra.
I'm sure.
Magnificent.
The stage is packed with so many people.
Yes, that's right. It's amazing.
I want you all to do it. I wonder if they want to hear this.
I have to do it.
I'm going to return all the compliments.
It's almost Brazil.
It's a city.
Goodbye secrets.
It's your kind of hint.
I can't spoil it.
It's pretty awesome you guys are saying.
Ho-ho-ho. I see.
I won't say what it is, but sometimes it's right.
You may be right.
That's true. If I say so much.
There are a few songs that are right, so please look forward to it.
Please look forward to it.
Next, let's see what's next.
There are still lots of tickets available for the 22nd and the 7th, right?
That's right. The 22nd is bright. We also have distribution.
How many friends do you want me to make?
Please send the link to everyone you are connected to on LINE.
For now.
In the meantime, it would be great if you could send me all the ticket links.
Please do.
Now let's move on to the next topic.
Start the survey! Questionnaire survey started!
Which way will you go? I'm so happy!
I don't have any friends.
Awkward
Mom and Dad
Younger siblings
Older brothers and sisters
Cousins, etc.
TikTok, Twitter...
EX.
I'll be waiting for you.
Let's send it to the corporate line.
I hope that's okay.
I'll be happy if you come.
What will it be?
My cousin lives in England.
Can you stream overseas?
No.
Let's get him to come to Japan.
Let's get him on a plane and fly over!
Personally, I'm also interested in number 7.
That's for sure.
We'll discuss it.
I'll do it.
Five.
Four.
Three.
One.1
Thank you.
Don't you see what you've become?
Oh!
Number two?
Chief of police.
Chief of police for a day.
In Itabashi Ward.
That was a while ago.
Feels like a while ago.
My schedule's all packed up here.
Everything's been packed for New Zealand.
That's why it feels so long ago.
I'm surprised it feels that way.
It sure does.
We'll be the Itabashi District Police Chief for a day.
We're going to make him the chief of police for a day.
We got to see it.
It was amazing.
There were so many people.
So many people came to see us.
They took pictures and stuff.
I'm walking like this.
Everyone was walking around.
And when they're done taking pictures...
And when they're done taking pictures, they spin around once more.
It's not nice to meet you, is it?
One of them asked me if I thought it was fun.
That was amazing.
That was...That was...
But I was allowed to pass through the shopping arcade.
In that shopping arcade...
The stores in the shopping arcade looked delicious.
There was a store that sold okara doughnuts.
They look so delicious!
I want to try some oshirisobo!
It's got two fashionable things on it, a fashionable thing and a thirty-bun!
Wow, that was...
That was fun.
You know what?
Yuna...
She's a real cop.
I don't know...
I don't know if you borrowed it.
I just...
Yuna's here.
They know you're Gizania.
They know who you are.
She's so cute.
She was cute.
I mean...
I mean, the costumes...
The uniform.
You know, Kaho...
You look like that no matter what you wear.
It looked great on you.
Are you working?
It's a short, beautiful police uniform.
Just like that.It was like...
That was so beautiful.
And the fact that you're a short cup was amazing.
You can do it right.
You do it right every time.
I think it's great.
That was great.
And afterwards, you know.
I got to go on a talk show.
And helmets.
And YoonA.
From the makeup.
You had already made up your mind before.
There were so many helmets on display.
I was like, "Which one do you want?
The cool ones.
You seemed quick.
But...
I was in the middle of the police work.
"I bought a helmet after I was on the police squad.
I was very happy to hear that.
To all of you.
Please wear it!
And you know what?
You know that Peepo doll I got you?
You know, the stuffed animal?
I got a really big one.
The manager said...
Yesterday at work.I was at work yesterday.
I'm sitting in the women's seat in the car.
The manager was riding with her like this.
Pipo-kun.
I'm making good use of it.
Yes, indeed.
From the outside, from a police officer's point of view.
"A car with Mr. Peepo on it
They might think it's safe to drive with Mr. Peepo.
I've been riding around with a stuffed animal like that
I've been riding in the morning with a stuffed animal like this.
I think it was great.
Pepo-kun looked pretty funny, didn't he?
I don't know.
Look how happy he is.
That's great.
We're making good use of it.
So thank you very much for coming.
Shall we go to the next one?
Okay, let's go to the next one.
Yuna says that number 7 is...
I want you to pick one.
I definitely want to talk to you today.
It's okay.
You don't have to choose.
I don't mind if you don't.
I mean, if you could, like, comment on my Instagram or something.
Or you can just send me a bunch of these.
I want to talk about it.
On Instagram. Insta.
This is what all the comments on my insta posts and stuff are about.
I'd better take it with me.
They're all so long.
They're all really long.
Oh, no.
Pradlibs.
I wonder what it is.
Oh, it's over. Well then, the survey is over!
How did you like it? How did it go?
You guys are so nice! Thank you very much. This is on the subject of what we want to talk about together.
What is Searsap? I'm going to New Zealand, so I'd like to know if there is anything you think would be useful to have when traveling abroad.
I'd like to know if there is anything that you think would be useful when traveling abroad. I heard that it is very cold in New Zealand. I heard it's really cold in New Zealand.
I heard it's really cold in New Zealand. So I think I can buy a down jacket or something like that in New Zealand.
I bought some heated eggs. I bought some fronties. I bought a Barker. I bought an outlet converter.
I got Wi-Fi. I got a compression bag. I bought onigiri (rice balls) that you just pour hot water into.
I bought miso soup. And what else?
I bought slippers for the plane.
And of course, my passport.
I heard that eggs, mystery meat, and grass are not allowed. It's hard to know what's not allowed.
I bought a neck pillow from a famous online store again, but it hasn't arrived yet.
I'm thinking of buying it the day after tomorrow.
I almost bought it at the Civil Engineering Hotel, at the Clothing Cloth and Three Coins.
They sell everything. Thank God. I bought an eye mask.
It's hard work.
Nola Shoes probably won't get it anymore.
I've been waiting for Nola shoes.
They're already gone from my order list.
I don't know what to do about that.
It can't be helped.It can't be helped.
What is it?
I bought the voltage.
Voltage?
Voltage is that thing, right?
You know, the kind you plug into an outlet or something, so I bought that.
The converter? It's a large outlet for New Zealand.
Yes, yes, yes.
I've never heard of it before.
Is this our first time abroad?
Since it will be my first time abroad, there are so many things I really don't know, so I mostly asked Mirei to help me.
Mirei is amazing.
Almost every day.
Have you ever bought this?
What is this?
I'm really sorry.
It's an extension cord.
I have to get an extension cord.
You're saying you want me to get more?
Yeah.
I have so much stuff that I'm preparing, but I'm not sure if it's going to fit in my carry-on case.
I'm not sure about the switch.
Switch?
Like at night?
But, you know, it was surprisingly good at night, too.
For sure.
Sure, sure.
Detergent. Detergent, too.
I bought detergent and a small pair of clothespins.
Really? Really?
Well, let's have you be Yumemi for a minute.
You know, we're all about cooperation here.
Okay. We all need to work together.
Okay.
I'm in charge of card games.
I'm in charge of card games, yes. I have a lot of stories here.
So, you know, a game called Her, or something fun like that.
I think I should bring some playing cards and Uno,
I'm responsible for that.
I'm in charge of hair ornaments, and I'm in charge of all the members' hair ornaments?
For the time being, there will be some location shooting only for the younger members,
I will bring a lot of hair ornaments.
Yes, I'll bring a lot of hair ornaments. I will borrow them.
I'm in charge of hair ornaments.
A belly band.
A spare compression bag. They get torn up pretty easily.
Is that so?
I used the regular cloth type, so it'll probably be fine.
That one. I see. That's true.
I'm a little scared of the bag.
This story will go on forever.
That's right.
What about New Zealanders? You know what I mean?
You know what I'm saying?
Is that it? There it is.
It's in that song.
Come on, Wellington.
What?
Wait. Wait for this.
What? I think it's Auckland or Oceania.
Auckland.
Me and, oh, no.
I thought it was Wellington because it's in the lyrics of the song "Lonerdon".
Oh, yeah.
Huh? That's right.
It was a strike. That Wellington.
Wellington.
Where's Auckland?
Wellington is the biggest place.
The biggest place is Sto.
That's Hokkaido in Japan, where people aren't from.
I see.
Artificial agreement.
Oh, I see.
You'll probably come with Eno and the others, right?
That's right.
Well, I'm looking forward to it.
The area you'll be taking care of, huh?
I'll use my phone to see the weather and stuff,
I'm going to be in Oakland.
The area you'll be taking care of.
I'll be looking out for you.
Australia is in there too.
I forgot when I said that.
That's what came up. Really.
So it's the weather in general? That's right.
It looked cold.
I converted it properly into New Zealand dollars, too.I converted it properly to New Zealand dollars, too.
I converted it.
If you need anything else, I'm here for you guys,
How do I do this? I might post it on my insta-story or something,
I might post it on my insta-story or something.
If you could get back to me within a minute or two, that would be great.
Next question?
Already a problem?
Do you have any more?
Or none?
Last survey.
Don.
I'm out of all of this, well, everything.
Yes, I guess so.
Yes, I know.
But 3, 4, and 5 are the ones that haven't been hit so far.
Any number of times, even kamebushi.
It's a kamebushi, isn't it?
Not more than this.
Always on your mind? The last sound.
I'm curious about the ice cream.
Oh.
Ice cream is something you eat every day.
It's delicious.
Sanganazo.
Ooh.
So, what's going to happen now?
Let's see,
Five, four, three, two, one. Five, four, three, two, one.
Yes.
Now, let's see what we got.
Yes, sir.
Number 3.
This is what Yuno wants to talk about,
I was thinking that the sound of the t'rung after the t'rung after the t'rung after the t'rung after the t'rung is definitely different.
Today, when I was looking around, where do you think the t'ung sound is?
I think it is,
I think it's the same.
Wait a minute, don't say this.
Where do you think it is?
I'm looking at it right now.
Everyone, just say "Tung" on the train right now.
Just say it.
It's okay. You won't even know if I just say that one word.
That's right.
I don't think too many people would be able to guess the sound.
Well, those of you who have absolute pitch, please try to guess the piano's, you know..,
The sound of "Pa".
The note "p", you know.
An octave lower.
That's right.
Trunten, trunten.
Right.
Wow, people are trying to tell me with their comments somehow.
The correct answer is, um, I don't know how to say it like an octave below heaven or something,
Trunten, Trunten, Trun.
Ah.Ah.
I see.
So, you know, COCO-NA, you know, the sound of "poon," and "t-run-ten, t-run-ten, t-run-ten, t-run-ten, t-run-ten," right?
That's right. Me too.
That's why I wanted to tell you that it's "toon.
By the way, when I was in elementary school, that was the sound you made with your nose, so it was very popular.
So, it was very popular. But it's just "t-thump", "t-thump", "t-thump".
The correct answer is to go down.
So I said, "That's wrong.
Right. So I thought everyone was different, and, you know, when I was lying down and looking around, I found it.
Oh, well, you know, I had everyone I met do a little bit of this.
With a lot of confidence.
Oh? Oh, you're a mimisso-mimisso.
Oh, actually, I did it an octave.
Wow, you can tell that you went an octave.
You can tell when you've gone an octave.
You can tell that you went up an octave.
That's what I was saying. You should tell this to all kinds of people with your chest out.
Maybe you can tell them to say "Tung" for a while.
It's a good topic of conversation.
Do you have such a sense of pitch, Mr. Nonaka?
I can play the piano, but I don't have absolute pitch, you know, like the sound of a song,
I can generally recognize the sound of a piano note when I hear it on the piano, but not absolutely.
Wow, that's amazing.
So, new songs, that's exactly what I mean,
You asked for the sheet music, didn't you?
Yes, I get the sheet music, and if I don't understand a note, I play it on the piano and see how it sounds.
I do that kind of thing.
Wow, that's amazing. Well, that's great.
Yes, that's right, everyone.
Please try to say Tung.
Yes, I will. That's all I have to say,
So, that's all for now.
Yes. Next up,
Now, I'm going to do a project like this.
A fun and fufufu Halloween that's too comical to be conveyed.
Yay.
Yes. This is a project that we always do every October,
Users are asked to comment on the characters that we can't get across because they're too cute,
We then suddenly become the character,
Yes, that's how we do it. That's how this project works.
I remember, you know, people who think they know the rules of rugby,
We are talking normally, and then suddenly they start to play the role of a person who pretends to know the rules of rugby,
What kind of rugby?
How many kinds of rugby?
I mean, do you know the rules of rugby? The rules.
Maybe you don't know much about it.
It's a kind of ball, a little round ball, whatever it is,
You kick it and swing it high.
Oh, I see.
I'm going to do it like that,
Please send me your characters that are too small to be understood.
Yes, I'll do it. It's already October, so spring is fine. Let's start with spring.
Which do you want to do first?
I haven't decided which one to do first.
Well, let's do it when we find a good one.
Oh, okay. So it's like we're going to start suddenly. Oh, okay. So it's like you're suddenly starting to do it.
Yes.
I'm going to call you Mom by mistake.
Emma did that yesterday.
Yes, she did.
She called the manager "Mom.
That's right. Call her a teacher.
She actually used to be a teacher.
Right.
What's wrong?
Hmm?
I wonder how long it'll take me to finish this delivery.
Something to do with trains?
Yeah. Something like that?
Uh, what? What's wrong?
Uh, yeah. It's nothing.
Who are you?
I'm someone who wants to rent soon, but can't seem to find the right time.
I know, right? I understand. I totally understand.
I'd like to rent a room as soon as possible,
But if I leave now, it's not the right time.
Yes, that's true.
Well, I've already started,
If you find something good, I'd like to have you do it, too,
What?
Oh?
Oh!
She's the kind of person who gets up thinking she's getting off at the station she's getting off at, but she's not, so she sits down while cheating.
Did you do it today?
Yesterday.I did it yesterday.
I was surprised when I dozed off,
I thought it was a train station, but it wasn't.
It's embarrassing.
Yuu, you just said, "Next is the station. Next is the station. I was about to get off the train, so I got off and went to the next station,
I almost got off the train, so I got off and changed to a different place once.
It's embarrassing, you know.
What happened?
[Hajime Shacho's ending]
Who are you?
I'm the person who gets irritated when I'm about to sneeze and I don't.
That's why I don't sneeze.
Really.
I want to concentrate on sneezing, but I get hit by it.
It was popular once among the members, wasn't it?
It was popular.
If you say "sneeze" right before you sneeze, people stop sneezing.
It stops. I really don't like this.
No, it's the sneezing that makes you stop.
I've heard that before.
I have a friend who has a record of sneezing when she doesn't sneeze, like she sneezes when she looks at the sun,
If I get out of the car in the dark, I definitely sneeze.
If I get out of the car?
It's not so bright in the car.
Yes, it is. It's dark.
That's why I go out,
Is it the same? When it gets light.
When you lighten up, I'll go out.
I'm here.
I'm here, I'm here. I know you're out there.
It was funny to see him wearing a mask.
I gave up on saying it.
It's hard to comment on this one.
I'll see what I can come up with. I wonder if there is anything.
I'll see what I can find.
What's up?
Anything?
Someone says that if you put light in your nose, you'll sneeze.
Is that so?
No way.
Is that true?
I wonder if there's anything to it.
I wonder if there is.
I don't know what to do. I don't know what to do.
I don't know what to do. What should I do?
I think people are commenting a lot of things.
There are a lot.
But I think it's true, because there are some people who say they put light in their nose.
They put a light in their nose.
It's good, isn't it?
Look at the pollen, isn't it bad these days?
It's terrible.
I have hay fever,
I have hay fever.
I don't have hay fever.
Really? Who are you?
Someone who doesn't have hay fever but suffers from hay fever.
I know there are people who have hay fever.
Yes, there are. There are those who are there.
There are people who don't admit to hay fever as a catapult.
Yes, there are. They say, "I don't have hay fever.
I say I have hay fever.
I have hay fever, too.
I'm in a lot of club activities right now.
Who are you?
I'm a person whose Doraemon imitation is hopelessly similar to Doraemon's.
Is it similar?
It's hard...
There are people who look like me, but there is almost no one who can say, "I look like this.
Right! What should I do in such a situation?
How should I react?
Should I say "wow"? It's hard to know.
That's what copers do.
That's for sure.
Cocona's boy is just strong.
Shin-chan?
You said it strongly anyway.
It's funny, but it's like I'm saying it with a lot of energy.
Sometimes I do all of them like Crayon Shin-chan's imitation,
Cocona comes in.
Mire-chan is Ne-chan,
Mire-chan is Ne-chan and Mayama-san is Masao-kun.
They look so much alike.
Kaho is like Crayon Shin-chan.
The three of them look pretty much alike, but then, Boy comes in.
What? You think so?
Everyone says they don't look like him. Everyone says he doesn't look like a little boy, he doesn't look like a little boy.
It's interesting.
You do all kinds of stuff.
Who are you?
The one who puts too much vinegar on fried rice
Who puts vinegar on fried rice?
I put it in ramen noodles and so on.
I often hear that it is good to put it in when you want to change the taste.
But I don't like to put too much vinegar because I don't want it to taste sour.
So I don't put too much vinegar.
No?
My least favorite seasoning is balsamic vinegar.
I see. Balsamic vinegar.
That's why I don't like vinegar.
You know those fancy salads with balsamic vinegar on them?
I really wish they'd stop.
You're right. I heard it's fashionable.
With little leaves on top.
Just use sesame seeds.
You're right.
I thought MacDonald's had the best salad.
It's the best.
That's for sure.
Don't worry about the balsamic vinegar on it.
Maybe there's some that you don't even know have it.
That's what I'm saying.
We both had the same one.
We both blinked too much.
We're the ones who blink too much.
Who are you? Who are you?
Someone who blinks too much.
Maybe it's the blink of an eye.
I blink a lot.
Too many blinks?
I blink too much during music videos.
The music video for "Earphone Lion" is pretty obvious.
You blink a lot.
Really?
I've always blinked a lot.
What's wrong?
You're the one who wants to sleep, but you're trying so hard to hold it in.
This is Ema, isn't it? This is...
This is, you know, yesterday, too.
Yesterday, too, I was busy with someone else.
When she was doing her makeup, she was, you know, thumping and thumping. It was amazing.
The makeup artist's face.
Yuna is already sleeping like this.
Yes, yes, yes. Yuna's neck shifts.
When she sleeps sitting down, she sleeps like this, then like this.
Yes, Yuna. You are sleeping, aren't you?
Yesterday, she was trying her best to hold it in even though she wanted to sleep.
Oh, really?
Yesterday, I decided to get my nails done on a whim,
I went to get my nails done, and when I was getting them done, I was like this, and I was trying so hard to keep my eyes open like this.
When it shakes.
Yes. I was on a table, so I put one in the light and did it like this.
Wow, it's so cute.
It's warm here.
Oh, no.Wow, oh no.
It's warm and I've been sitting here forever.
Yeah, it's a little foggy, isn't it?
Yeah.
Who are you?
Someone who wants to whistle, but can't.
Uh...
Can you whistle?
Me?
Yes, I can.
I used to be able to whistle, but I can't anymore.
Oh, wait, I can't.
I really can't.
You can't play it... right?
If you make a zipper-like sound, you can do it, right?
You've got a great voice.
I think I can do it with my voice, but I can't do it with my voice.
Sometimes you're really good at it... no matter where you learned it, you still lose... I can't do the "tororo"...
I can't do the next one.
Trollo, Trollo, Trollo...
I can't do it.
But I can't do this one because I don't have to
That's right.
Who are you?
I'm the guy who eats kukulet rice balls in class.
But you know what? These are onigiri.
Because it looked like an onigiri.
Have you ever eaten onigiri during class?
No, I have not.
Yes, I have. There's that one.
Keep the bread in the drawer,
No, no, no, I was in class after lunch,
I was a little short.
About a second before the teacher started class,
I'd stick it in my mouth and chew it so it wouldn't fall out.
Okay, that's not a problem.
It's okay, I can't help it. He was nice.
I hated pool class after I became an idol in ninth grade,
You hated it so much.
You hated it.
So you took a day off.
It wasn't a magic mirror,
I couldn't see it from here,
And the teachers are by the pool,
So nothing came.
So I had dinner with my friends.
You're doing a good job, aren't you?
But I couldn't see them.
The gold tape only came to the first floor, and the people on the second floor looked sad.
Sad.
You know, this is like a birthday party.
I was allowed to go to the birthday party.
I went to see you.
At birthday festivals, the first thing that happens is that people go up to the stage with pans.
The first floor is full of people.
The second floor seats only came from the front.
So, I was at the front and it was around the end of the show.
So there was time for an encore, So there was time for an encore,
That's when the encore happens, and the people upstairs go downstairs to get it. Everyone.
They went to the front of the second floor.
It was really interesting to see them take it back down and come back up.
It was awkward.
It would be nice if they went a little higher up.
I wonder if it was that time when I asked Osaku-san to go upstairs to the second floor, and then he popped.
It was a manual operation.
With a "pan".
After he finishes picking up the pieces.
That might be a good idea.
It would give me peace of mind.
Yes. That's all for now,
A funny, funny, too detailed and unused Halloween.
Yes. And so, the 62nd edition of the delightful and hilarious Shower Room is quickly coming to an end.
Yes, it's coming to an end. Here is an announcement.
There were many announcements.
You drew a lot of pictures for the announcements.
Yes, I did.
Yes, I did. The first one is tomorrow.
Wait for now?
Oh, please.
Private Art Junior High School Okera Disco 2023 will be held tomorrow, Saturday, October 7, at Pacifico Yokohama National Hall, and on Sunday, October 22, at Hall A of Tokyo International Hall,
and Sunday, October 22nd at Hall A of the Tokyo International Hall.
Tickets are still available and will be distributed on the 22nd,
Please send the link to all your friends on LINE and come to the show.
Please send the link to all your friends on LINE.
Please send the link to all of your friends on LINE. And...,
There it is!
Here it is. This is Yuu's dragon picture.Yes. This is Yu, the picture of the dragon.
It's interesting. This is interesting.
Private Art Junior High School New Year's Grand Art Exhibition 2024
Takakura Mauryu and Beyond Us
Saturday, January 6 and Sunday, January 7, 2024 next year
It will be held at Pialina MM in 2den.
The reason why this was not good is my lips.
I think my lips were a little too big.
It didn't work.
Until then, you know, I saw it on Instagram.
Tickets are still on sale.
I hope you have time to send them to your friends here, too.
I'll be there next year. The link will be up next year.
Please spread the word.
I hope you will spread the word.
Now, I would like to announce the final ranking.
I will start from the 5th place.
First, 5th place
Mr. Endo.
Thank you very much.
Fourth place, Keibun.
Third place, Okkun-san.
Thank you very much.
2nd place, Mr. Miriri.
1st, Baachii-san.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. And that's it.
That's the end of the 62nd edition of Ebitune's Delightful and Fluffy Showroom. This is the end of the 62nd edition of Ebitune's Delightful and Fluffy Showroom.
The next distribution will be announced as soon as it is decided.
And, as there will be no reflection today...
Was there anything to reflect on?
Was there anything?
I rattled too much today.
That's right. I was a little too familiar with the house and didn't know when it started and when it ended.
I want to ring it a lot from now on, and I'll do it next time.
That's right. I'll be sure to do that.
I was sometimes in Ebitune during the first session.
Ah, I see. I see.
I hear that a lot.
I guess I can wait until the end.
Let's do that.
Yes, I will. So that's it.
Ah, yes.
Then, let's say goodbye.
Let's see...
We will let you know the next delivery as soon as it is decided.
So, that's it.
That's all for Private Art Middle School.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.